Hey, I'm Tobi.
大家好 我叫 Tobi
And I'm Ben.
大家好 我叫 Ben
And we are software engineers at Mercedes-Benz,
我们是 Mercedes-Benz 公司的软件工程师
who work in the behavior planning team.
在行为规划团队工作
The behavior planning team is responsible for providing guidance to
行为规划团队负责为轨迹规划器提供引导工作
the trajectory planner about what sorts of maneuvers they should plan trajectories for.
告诉规划器它将为何种类型的动作规划轨迹
If you think about the over all flow of data in
请大家思考一下 在时间以极快速度变化情况下
a self-driving car operating on the fastest time scales you have control.
某个无人驾驶车操控的整体数据流
And with a slightly lower frequency than that you have Sensor Fusion.
传感器工作频率仅比运动控制模块略低
Just lower than that you have localization and
在传感器之上 是工作频率更低的定位模块和轨迹规划模块
trajectory planning which you learn more about in a next lesson.
大家将在下一课中学习轨迹规划
Next is Prediction which you just learned about.
然后是大家刚学过的预测模块
And then at the top of this diagram is behavior planning with the lowest update rate.
在这张图的顶部便是行为规划模块 该模块具有最低的更新频率
The inputs to behavior planning come from
行为规划模块的输入
the prediction module and the localization module.
来自预测模块和定位模块
Both of which get their inputs from the sensor fusion.
预测模块和定位模块则从传感器融合获取输入
And the output from the behavior module goes directly to the trajectory planner.
行为模块的输出直接进入轨迹规划器
Which also takes input from prediction and
轨迹规划器同时也从预测模块和定位模块获取输入
localization so that it can send trajectories to the motion controller.
然后轨迹规划器发送轨迹到运动控制器
Everything inside of this box is the focus of
这个框里面的东西便是本课程的重点
this course and is commonly referred to as Path Planning.
所有这些通常被称为 路径规划(Path Planning)
In this lesson, you will learn what exactly has to
在本课程中 大家将学习
happen in this comparatively long time span.
在这个相对较长的时间段里 到底会发生哪些事情
But intuitively this longtime span comes from
但是从图上 大家可以看出
the fact that the behavior plan has to incorporate a lot of
时间段之所以较长
data to make decisions about
是因为行为规划需要获取大量或数据 然后才能做出决策
fairly long time horizons in the order of 10 seconds or even more.
这个过程需要大约10秒或者更长时间
We will start by doing a brief introduction where
我们会从一个简短的介绍开始
you'll learn more about the details of the inputs and
从介绍里 你将了解到更多
outputs to behavior planner and understand
有关行为规划器的输入输出细节信息
what problems a behavior planning module is expected to solve.
并理解行为规划器要解决的问题
Next, we will talk about
接下来
Finite State Machines as one technique for implementing a behavior plan.
我们会讨论有限状态机 这是一种实现行为规划的技术
Followed by a more in-depth look at
然后我们会深入讲解成本函数
the Cost Functions we will use to actually make behavioral level decisions.
我们会使用成本函数 来真正做出行为级别的决策
But first let's spend some time looking at the inputs
但是现在 我们还需要花一些时间来了解一下
we would be working with and the outputs we will be generating.
整个过程需要的输入 以及将会生成的输出